You just read about how everything is a number, but let's see how this principle
你刚刚读到所有事物都是数字，但让我们看看这个原则
applies to some things that may not seem like numbers at first glance.
如何适用于一些乍一看可能不像数字的东西。
Strings are numbers,
字符串是数字，
you have seen literal sequences of characters before, such as Hello World!
你以前见过字面上的字符序列，比如 Hello World！
But did you think about how the computer stores them as numbers?
但是你有没有想过电脑是如何将它们存储为数字的？
Each character occupies some of the computer's memory.
每个字符都会占用计算机的部分内存。
We'll talk about exactly how much later, so
稍后我们将具体讨论多少，这样
you can think of each character conceptually in a box.
你就可以在一个盒子里从概念上考虑每个角色。
In terms of hardware though, the computer stores each character as a number.
但是，就硬件而言，计算机将每个字符存储为一个数字。
You can look up the decimal or hexadecimal values of different characters in an ASCII
您可以在 ASCII
table, and you can see the decimal values of these particular characters here.
表中查找不同字符的十进制或十六进制值，也可以在此处查看这些特定字符的十进制值。
Of course, the computer stores them as binary numbers.
当然，计算机会将它们存储为二进制数。
One fun consequence of computers storing letters as numbers
计算机将字母存储为数字的一个有趣结果
is that we can do math on them.
是，我们可以对它们进行数学运算。
This principle underlies most modern methods of cryptography.
这一原则是大多数现代密码学方法的基础。起@@
Another thing that may not seem to be a number at first is an image,
初可能看起来不是数字的另一件事是一张图像，
like this one of some flowers.
比如一些花中的一张。
This image is made of about a million pixels,
该图像由大约一百万个像素
which each numerically represent the colors in the image.
组成，每个像素都用数字表示图像中的颜色。
To see these pixels, let's zoom in on this small section of the image.
要查看这些像素，让我们放大图像的这一小部分。
Here, you can see the image magnified several times.
在这里，您可以看到图像被放大了几倍。
You can see how this image looks blocky or pixelated.
你可以看到这张图片看起来像块状或像素化。
This is what the image actually looks like if you could look that closely.
如果你能仔细观察，这就是图像的实际样子。
Note that if you try this yourself,
请注意，如果你自己尝试一下，
you might end up with something that looks much smoother like this.
你最终可能会得到像这样看起来更流畅的东西。
Most image software will apply algorithms to smooth out the pixelation when you
当你
enlarge an image.
放大图像时，大多数图像软件都会应用算法来平滑像素化。
You have to turn that off to see the original pixels.
你必须将其关闭才能看到原始像素。
Let us return to our enlarged image that shows the original pixels more clearly.
让我们回到放大的图像，它可以更清晰地显示原始像素。
If we look only at a subset of this image, and blow it up even further,
如果我们只看这张图像的子集，然后把它放得更远，
we can see and talk about the individual pixels more easily.
我们就能更容易地看到和谈论各个像素。
Here are 16 pixels from the original image, which had about a million pixels,
以下是原始图像的16个像素，大约有100万个像素，
just to give you an idea of how much we have zoomed in now.
只是为了让你大致了解我们现在放大了多少。
This dark purple pixel has a red value of 55, a green value of 27,
此深紫色像素的红色值为 55，绿色值为 27
and a blue value of 75.
，蓝色值为 75。
Meanwhile, this golden pixel has drastically different RGB values,
同时，这个金色像素具有截然不同的RGB值，分别
166, 136, and 41, giving it an entirely different color.
为166、136和41，因此它的颜色完全不同。
Sound is another important thing that computers process.
声音是计算机处理的另一件重要事情。
As I'm talking, you can see the waveforms of what I'm saying.
在我说话的时候，你可以看到我所说的话的波形。
The computer encodes these as numbers and sends them to the sound hardware,
计算机将它们编码为数字，然后将其发送到声音硬件，声音硬件
which uses them to determine how to move the speaker generating the desired sound.
使用它们来确定如何移动扬声器以产生所需的声音。
There are many other types of data you might want to represent and compute on.
您可能还需要表示和计算许多其他类型的数据。
You'll learn about data that is formed from sequences in Course 3.
你将在课程 3 中学习由序列形成的数据。
For now, you're going to learn about structs and typedefs.
现在，你将学习结构和类型定义。